Guide to the Duke University Archives Photographic Negative Collection, 1855-1995
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Numbered Negatives
  - Negatives 601-1200 (Box 45)
    - n950 Gross, Paul
    - n951 Gross, Paul
    - n952 Gross, Paul, 1965
    - n953 Gross, Paul
    - n954 Gross, Paul
    - n955 Gross, Paul
    - n956 Gross, Paul
    - n957 Haines, Howard
    - n958 Hall, Frank
    - n959 Hall, Frank
    - n960 Hall, Frank
    - n961 Hall, Frank
    - n962 Hall, Frank
    - n963 Hall, Louise
    - n964 Hall, Thor
    - n965 Hall, William Holland
    - n966 Hamblin, Edwing
    - n967 Hamblin, Edwing
    - n968 Hamblin, Edwing
    - n969 Hamilton, Earl
    - n970 Hamilton, William
    - n971 Hanes, P. Huber
    - n972 Hanks, Nancy
    - n973 Hanks, Nancy
    - n974 Hanna, Frank
    - n975 Hanson, Earl
    - n976 Hargitt, George Thomas, 1937
    - n977 Hargitt, George Thomas, 1936
    - n978 Harrar, Scotty
    - n979 Harrar, Scotty
    - n980 Missing from box
    - n981 Harrar, Scotty, 1937
    - n982 Hartman, David
    - n983 Hartman, David
    - n984 Hart, Hornell
    - n985 Hart, Hornell, 1946
    - n986 Hart, Hornell, 1946
    - n987 Hart, Hornell
    - n988 Hart, Hornell
    - n989 Hart, Hornell
    - n990 Hart, Julian Deryl
    - n991 Hart, Julian Deryl
    - n992 Hart, Julian Deryl
    - n993 Hart, Julian Deryl
    - n994 Hasbrouck, Francis, 1938
    - n995 Hauser, Charles R.
    - n996 Hauser, Charles R.
    - n997 Hendrix, Mildred
    - n998 Hendrix, Mildred
    - n999 Hendrix, Mildred
    - n1000 Hendrix, Mildred
    - n1001 Heninger, S. K. Jr.
    - n1002 Heninger, S. K.
    - n1003 Missing from box
    - n1004 Missing from box
    - n1005 Missing from box
    - n1006 Herring, Herbert
    - n1007 Herring, Herbert
    - n1008 Herring, Herbert
    - n1009 Herring, Herbert
    - n1010 Herring, Herbert
    - n1011 Hickman, Frank
    - n1012 Hickman, Frank
    - n1013 Hickson, A. O., 1937
    - n1014 Hickson, A. O.
    - n1015 Hill, Douglas
    - n1016 Hill, Robert, 1969 June
    - n1017 Hillerbrand, Hans J., 1969
    - n1018 Hobbs, Marcus Edwin
    - n1019 Hohman, Leslie
    - n1020 Hohman, Leslie
    - n1021 Holler, Walker
    - n1022 Holton, Holland
    - n1023 Hoover, C. B., 1939
    - n1024 Hoover, C. B., 1937
    - n1025 Hoover, C. B.
    - n1026 Hoover, C. B.
    - n1027 Hoover, C. B.
    - n1028 Hoover, C. B.
    - n1029 Hoover, C. B.
    - n1030 Hopkins, Everett
    - n1031 Hopkins, Everett
    - n1032 Hopkins, Everett
    - n1033 Horack, H. C., 1938
    - n1034 Horn, E. C.
    - n1035 Horn, E. C.
    - n1036 Howell, Doris, 1957
    - n1037 Hubbell, Dr. J. B.
    - n1038 Huckabee, Ellen
    - n1039 Heustis, Charles B.
    - n1040 Humphrey, Don
    - n1041 Humphrey, Don
    - n1042 Hunt, Samuel Robert
    - n1043 Hurlburt, Allan
    - n1044 Huxley, Aldous, 1937
    - n1045 Hyman, Mac
    - n1046 Ilkow, Peter
    - n1047 Missing from box
    - n1048 Ingram, O. Kelly
    - n1049 Jacobansky, Ann
    - n1050 Jayne, Benjamin
    - n1051 Missing from box
    - n1052 Jeffers, Katherine
    - n1053 Jennings, Ralph
    - n1054 Jensen, Howard
    - n1055 Jensen, Howard
    - n1056 Jensen, Howard
    - n1057 Jensen, Howard
    - n1058 Jensen, Howard
    - n1059 Jensen, Howard
    - n1060 Johnson, Charles E.
    - n1061 Jones, Barney
    - n1062 Jones, Randolph
    - n1063 Jones, William P.
    - n1064 Jordan, Archibald
    - n1065 Jordan, Brady
    - n1066 Jordan, Brady
    - n1067 Jurgenson, Sonny
    - n1068 Kale, William Arthur
    - n1069 Kanter, George
    - n1070 Jordan, Charles Edward
    - n1071 Jordan, Charles Edward
    - n1072 Jordan, Charles Edward
    - n1073 Jordan, Charles Edward
    - n1074 Jordan, Charles Edward
    - n1075 Jordan, Charles Edward
    - n1076 Jordan, Charles Edward
    - n1077 Jordan, Charles Edward
    - n1078 Jordan, Charles Edward
    - n1079 Kempner, Walter
    - n1080 Kempner, Walter
    - n1081 Kennedy, John Fitzgerald
    - n1082 Kennedy, John Fitzgerald
    - n1083 Kilgo, John C.
    - n1084 Kilgo, John C.
    - n1085 Kilgo, John C.
    - n1086 Kilgo, John C.
    - n1087 Kilgo, John C.
    - n1088 Kilgo, John C.
    - n1089 Kilgo, Fannie
    - n1090 Kilgo, John C.
    - n1091 Kilgo, Mrs. John C.
    - n1092 Kilgo, Fannie
    - n1093 King, Martin Luther Jr.
    - n1094 King, Martin Luther Jr.
    - n1095 King, Martin Luther Jr.
    - n1096 Kinney, Thomas, 1964
    - n1097 Kinney, Thomas, 1960 May
    - n1098 Klavins, Janis, 1961
    - n1099 Klenz, William, 1960
    - n1100 Klenz, William, 1960
    - n1101 Knight, Douglas M., portrait
    - n1102 Knight, Douglas M., portrait
    - n1103 Knight, Douglas M., group photo
    - n1104 Knight, Douglas M., group photo
    - n1105 Knight, Douglas M., inauguration
    - n1106 Knight, Douglas M., family, 1963 October
    - n1107 Knight, Douglas M., family, 1962
    - n1108 Knight, Douglas M., family, 1962
    - n1109 Knight, Douglas M., 1963
    - n1110 Knight, Douglas M., 1963
    - n1111 Knight, Douglas, M., 1963
    - n1112 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1113 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1114 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1115 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1116 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1117 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1118 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1119 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1120 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1121 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1122 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1123 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1124 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1125 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1126 Knight, Douglas M.
    - n1127 Kostyo, J.
    - n1128 Kramer, Paul
    - n1129 Knight, Douglas M., inauguration
    - n1130 Knight, Douglas M., inauguration
    - n1131 Korstian, Clarence with Mrs. Korstian
    - n1132 Korstian, Clarence
    - n1133 Korstian, Clarence
    - n1134 Korstian, Clarence
    - n1135 Korstian, Clarence
    - n1136 Korstian, Clarence, 1956
    - n1137 Kramer, Paul
    - n1138 Kramer, Paul
    - n1139 Kramer, Paul
    - n1140 Kreps, Juanita
    - n1141 Kreps, Juanita
    - n1142 Kreps, Juanita
    - n1143 Kreps, Juanita
    - n1144 Kulski, W.
    - n1145 LaBarre, Weston
    - n1146 LaBarre, Weston
    - n1147 LaBarre, Weston
    - n1148 LaBarre, Weston
    - n1149 Lacy, Creighton
    - n1150 Landon, Charles
    - n1151 Landon, Charles
    - n1152 Langford, Tom
    - n1153 Langford, Tom
    - n1154 Langford, Tom
    - n1155 Lanning, John Tate
    - n1156 LaPrade, William Thomas
    - n1157 LaPrade, William Thomas
    - n1158 LaPrade, William Thomas
    - n1159 LaPrade, William Thomas
    - n1160 LaPrade, William Thomas
    - n1161 LaPrade, William Thomas
    - n1162 LaPrade, William Thomas
    - n1163 LaPrade, William Thomas
    - n1164 LaPrade, William Thomas
    - n1165 LaPrade, William Thomas
    - n1166 Larson, Arthur
    - n1167 Larson, Arthur
    - n1168 Lassaw, Ibram
    - n1169 Latty, Elvin R.
    - n1170 Latty, Elvin R.
    - n1171 Latty, Elvin R.
    - n1172 Latty, Elvin R.
    - n1173 Latty, Elvin R.
    - n1174 Leighton, Clare
    - n1175 Linderoth, L. S., 1965
    - n1176 Lockwood, M. H.
    - n1177 Lockwood, M. H.
    - n1178 Lockwood, M. H.
    - n1179 London, Fritz
    - n1180 London, Fritz
    - n1181 Long, Johnny
    - n1182 Lowenbach, Hans
    - n1183 Lowndes, Charles L. B.
    - n1184 Lowndes, Charles L. B.
    - n1185 Lumiansky, Robert
    - n1186 Lumiansky, Robert
    - n1187 Lundeberg, O. K. (deteriorated, thrown-out)
    - n1188 McGeachy, Neill
    - n1189 McGee, Mike
    - n1190 McGee, Mike
    - n1191 Maggs, Douglas
    - n1192 Maggs, Douglas
    - n1193 Maguire, Robert
    - n1194 Manchester, Alan K.
    - n1195 Manchester, Alan K.
    - n1196 Manchester, Alan K.
    - n1197 Manchester, Alan K.
    - n1198 Manchester, Alan K.
    - n1199 Mann, Ted
    - n1200 Mann, Ted
  - Negatives 1201-1800 (Box 46)
    - n1201 Medical Center, Hospital South, aerial
    - n1202 Medical Center, Hospital South, lobby, 1938 November 7
    - n1203 Medical Center, Medical School, circa 1932
    - n1204 Medical Center, 1939 June
    - n1205 Medical Center, 1936-1937
    - n1206 Medical Center, sun porch, circa 1930-1932
    - n1207 Medical Center, circa 1928
    - n1208 Medical Center, Medical School, 1941 July
    - n1209 Medical Center, Medical School, circa 1929
    - n1210 Medical Center, circa 1937
    - n1211 Medical Center, circa 1937
    - n1212 Medical Center, construction, 1939 July
    - n1213 Medical Center, circa 1928
    - n1214 Medical Center, circa 1929
    - n1215 Medical Center, circa 1928-1929
    - n1216 Medical Center, circa 1928-1929
    - n1217 Medical Center, circa 1929
    - n1218 Medical Center, hyperbaric unit, drawing
    - n1219 Medical Center, library, circa 1938
    - n1220 Medical Center, construction, circa 1928
    - n1221 Medical Center, PDC construction, 1939 May 26
    - n1222 Medical Center, 1929
    - n1223 Medical Center, PDC construction, 1939 May 26
    - n1224 Medical Center, PDC construction, 1940 May
    - n1225 Medical Center, PDC construction, 1939 May 26
    - n1226 Medical Center, PDC construction, 1939 February 18
    - n1227 Medical Center, PDC construction, 1939 February 18
    - n1228 Medical Center, PDC construction, 1940 May
    - n1229 Medical Center, PDC construction, 1939 September
    - n1230 Medical Center, PDC construction, 1939 May 26
    - n1231 Medical Center, PDC construction, 1939 February 18
    - n1232 Medical Center, PDC construction, 1939 February 18
    - n1233 Medical Center, PRT
    - n1234 Medical Center, PRT
    - n1235 Orr, Louis, etching, Chapel
    - n1236 Orr, Louis, etching, Davison Building
    - n1237 Mary Duke Biddle Building
    - n1238 Mary Duke Building, Trinity College, Women's Dorm
    - n1239 Nixon caricature/cartoon
    - n1240 Durden, Robert
    - n1241 Campus Views, West Campus
    - n1242 Crowell Tower
    - n1243 Baldwin Auditorium, carving of seal is in error
    - n1244 Library, Trinity College, Durham
    - n1245 Decorations, West Campus, gargoyles
    - n1246 Decorations, West Campus, gargoyles
    - n1247 Baldwin Auditorium
    - n1248 Chapel roof construction, Prevatt/Stowman photos
    - n1249 Bassett, John Spencer
    - n1250 Missing from box
    - n1251 Primate Center, lemurs, West Campus
    - n1252 Snow Scenes, East Campus, 1980 January 31
    - n1253 Social Science (old Physics), from library tower, 1938 April 4
    - n1254 Soc-Psych Building (old Bio), West Campus
    - n1255 Soc-Psych Building, physiology lab, (old Bio)
    - n1256 Southgate Hall, East Campus, Aerial View
    - n1257 Southgate Hall, East Campus
    - n1258 Southgate Hall, Engineers Dorm, circa 1936-1938
    - n1259 Southgate Hall, construction, 1921
    - n1260 Southgate Hall, Trinity College
    - n1261 Southgate Hall, Alumni Register, 1931, page 150
    - n1262 Southgate Hall, East Campus
    - n1263 Statue, J. B. Duke, model, 1940
    - n1264 Statue, J. B. Duke, West Campus
    - n1265 Statue, J. B. Duke, 1970s
    - n1266 Statue, J. B. Duke, 1937
    - n1267 Statue, J. B. Duke, 1937
    - n1268 Statue, J. B. Duke, 1937
    - n1269 Statue, J. B. Duke, commencement, 1935
    - n1270 Statue, J. B. Duke, commencement, 1935
    - n1271 Statue, J. B. Duke, commencement, 1935
    - n1272 Statue, J. B. Duke, 1935 February
    - n1273 Statue, Washington Duke, 1937-1938
    - n1274 Statue, Washington Duke, circa 1919
    - n1275 Missing from box
    - n1276 Statue, Washington Duke, circa 1947
    - n1277 Statue, Washington Duke University
    - n1278 Statue, Washington Duke, Durham Sun, 1980 January 31
    - n1279 Statue, Washington Duke
    - n1280 Statue, Washington Duke, circa 1931
    - n1281 Statue, Sower (and girl)
    - n1282 Statue, Sower, East Campus
    - n1283 Statue, Sower, East Campus
    - n1284 Stonemason, working, Hillsborough
    - n1285 Trinity College Historical Society Museum
    - n1286 Union, East Campus, banquet, 1930s
    - n1287 Union, East Campus
    - n1288 Washington Duke Building, Trinity College, Room 11, circa 1897
    - n1289 Washington Duke Building, Trinity College
    - n1290 Washington Duke Building, Trinity College, after fire
    - n1291 Washington Duke Building, library, Trinity College
    - n1292 Washington Duke Building, after fire, 1911
    - n1293 Union, West Campus, construction, from Kilgo, circa 1928
    - n1294 Union, West Campus, exterior arcade, 1938
    - n1295 Union, West Campus, exterior back
    - n1296 Union, West Campus, interior Dope Shop
    - n1297 Union, West Campus, interior Dope Shop
    - n1298 Union, West Campus, interior Dope Shop
    - n1299 Union, West Campus, interior Dope Shop
    - n1300 Union, West Campus(?), Dope Shop
    - n1301 Union, West Campus, interior Dope Shop
    - n1302 Union, West Campus, interior Dope Shop
    - n1303 Union, West Campus, interior Dope Shop
    - n1304 Union, West Campus, interior Dope Shop
    - n1305 Union, West Campus, interior Dope Shop
    - n1306 Union, West Campus, interior Dope Shop
    - n1307 Union, West Campus, interior Dope Shop
    - n1308 Union, West Campus, interior Dope Shop
    - n1309 Union, West Campus, interior, Blue White Room
    - n1310 Wallace Wade Stadium, circa 1936-1938
    - n1311 Wallace Wade Stadium, aerial, circa 1950
    - n1312 Wallace Wade Stadium, aerial
    - n1313 Wallace Wade Stadium, aerial, Rose Bowl
    - n1314 Wallace Wade Stadium, aerial, 1939
    - n1315 Wallace Wade Stadium, aerial, 1929
    - n1316 Wallace Wade Stadium, aerial, crowd
    - n1317 Wallace Wade Stadium, aerial, 1935
    - n1318 Wallace Wade Stadium, construction
    - n1319 Wallace Wade Stadium, construction
    - n1320 Wallace Wade Stadium, construction, circa 1929 March
    - n1321 Wallace Wade Stadium, crowd, Duke vs. UNC, 1947
    - n1322 Wallace Wade Stadium, crowd
    - n1323 West Duke Building, East Campus
    - n1324 West Duke Building, Trinity College Bulletin, 1912
    - n1325 Decorations on buildings
    - n1326 Decorations on buildings
    - n1327 Decorations on buildings
    - n1328 Oates, John F., Roman plaque, 1976 March
    - n1329 Oates, John F., Roman plaque, 1976 March
    - n1330 Oates, John F., Roman plaque, 1976 March
    - n1331 Oates, John F., Roman plaque, 1976 March
    - n1332 Oosting, H. J. (with class), Franklin Co., NC, 1952
    - n1333 Orr, Louis, sketch, 1937 November
    - n1334 Outler, Albert C.
    - n1335 Overman, John R., 1956 February
    - n1336 Owens, Ida Virginia Stephens, first black female, PhD
    - n1337 Page, Walter H.
    - n1338 Parker, Clarence "Ace," 1936
    - n1339 Parker, Harold T., history seminar
    - n1340 Parker, Harold T.
    - n1341 Parker, Harold T.
    - n1342 Parker, John J.
    - n1343 Parrent, Allen M., 1964
    - n1344 Patrick, Ransom R., 1971 May
    - n1345 Patterson, Karl B.
    - n1346 Pearse, Arthur Sperry, 1937
    - n1347 Peele, Talmage Lee
    - n1348 Peele, William Walter
    - n1349 Pegram, William Howell
    - n1350 Penrod, Kenneth E.
    - n1351 Pepper, Joseph, 1963 October
    - n1352 Perkins, Thomas L.
    - n1353 Perkins, William
    - n1354 Perkins, William, painting
    - n1355 Perry, Edmund F., 1952 January
    - n1356 copy 1 Petry, Ray, 1962 September
    - n1356 copy 2 Petry, Ray, 1962 September
    - n1357 Petry, Ray, 1959 June
    - n1358 Petry, Ray, 1959 June
    - n1359 Phillips, Dr. Jay
    - n1360 Phillips, Dr. Jay, 1966 August
    - n1361 Phillips, Dr. Jay, 1965 February
    - n1362 Philpott, Jane
    - n1363 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, 1936
    - n1364 Politano, Victor, 1958 October
    - n1365 Poston, Mary, 1961 December
    - n1366 Poston, Mary, 1956 February
    - n1367 Poteat, J. D.
    - n1368 copy 1 Powell, Benjamin Edward
    - n1368 copy 2 Powell, Benjamin Edward
    - n1369 Powell, Benjamin Edward, 1963 September
    - n1370 Powell, Benjamin Edward, 1960
    - n1371 Powell, Benjamin Edward, 1960
    - n1372 Powell, Benjamin Edward, 1960 May
    - n1373 Powell, Benjamin Edward
    - n1374 Powell, Benjamin Edward
    - n1375 Powell, Benjamin Edward, 1960 May
    - n1376 Powell, Benjamin Edward, 1959 July
    - n1377 Predmore, Richard, 1967 October
    - n1378 Predmore, Richard, 1958 February
    - n1379 Predmore, Richard, 1958 February
    - n1380 Price, Reynolds, 1955 Chanticleer, page 84
    - n1381 Price, Reynolds
    - n1382 Price, Reynolds, 1963
    - n1383 Price, Reynolds
    - n1384 Price, Reynolds
    - n1385 Pye, Kenneth
    - n1386 Pye, Kenneth, 1968 August
    - n1387 Ralston, Charles William, 1968 November
    - n1388 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, statues
    - n1389 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, snow scenes
    - n1390 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, construction
    - n1391 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, dedication
    - n1392 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, statues
    - n1393 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, statues
    - n1394 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, statues
    - n1395 Sarah P. Duke Gardens, aerial views
    - n1396 Duke Gardens, woman by fountain
    - n1397 Sarah P. Duke Gardens
    - n1398 Rankin, Robert S. (deteriorated, thrown-out)
    - n1399 Ratchford, Benjamin, 1937
    - n1400 Ratchford, Benjamin, 1955 February
    - n1401 Reardon, Kenneth, 1963 October
    - n1402 Reamer, I. T., 1959 May
    - n1403 Reeves, Robert, 1958 November
    - n1404 Rhine, Joseph B.
    - n1405 Missing from box
    - n1406 Rhine, Joseph B.
    - n1407 Rhine, Joseph B.
    - n1408 Rhine, Joseph B.
    - n1409 Rhine, Joseph B.
    - n1410 Rhine, Joseph B.
    - n1411 copy 1 Rhine, Joseph B., portrait
    - n1411 copy 2 Rhine, Joseph B., portrait
    - n1412 Rhine, Joseph B., portrait
    - n1413 Rhoads, John M., 1961
    - n1414 Rivera, Rodolfo, circa 1937
    - n1415 Roalfe, William R., law, circa 1930
    - n1416 Robbins, Jeffrey H.
    - n1417 Robert, Joseph C., history, circa 1939
    - n1418 Roberts, J. H., math, 1966 August
    - n1419 Roberts, J. H.
    - n1420 Roll, W. G., 1960 March
    - n1421 copy 1 Roosevelt, Eleanor
    - n1421 copy 2 Roosevelt, Eleanor
    - n1422 Root, Paul A.
    - n1423 Ropp, Theodore, 1957 October
    - n1424 Ropp, Theodore
    - n1425 Ropp, Theodore, circa 1950
    - n1426 Rowe, Gilbert, circa 1937
    - n1427 Rowe, Gilbert, circa 1938
    - n1428 Rowe, Robert S., 1958 January
    - n1429 Rudin, Dr. John, circa 1953 June
    - n1430 Russell, Elbert, circa 1938
    - n1431 Russell, Elbert
    - n1432 Russell, Elbert
    - n1433 Russell, Mattie
    - n1434 Salinger, Herman, faculty, German, 1955 September
    - n1435 Sands, Alexander
    - n1436 Sanford, Terry, inauguration
    - n1437 Sanford, Terry, inauguration
    - n1438 Sanford, Terry, inauguration
    - n1439 Sanford, Terry, inauguration
    - n1440 Sanford, Terry, group photo
    - n1441 Sanford, Terry, group photo
    - n1442 Sanford, Terry, group photo
    - n1443 Sanford, Terry, group photo
    - n1444 Sanford, Terry, group photo
    - n1445 Sanford, Terry, group photo
    - n1446 Sanford, Terry, portrait
    - n1447 Sanford, Terry, portrait
    - n1448 Sanford, Terry, portrait
    - n1449 Sanford, Terry, portrait
    - n1450 Sanford, Terry, portrait
    - n1451 Sanford, Terry, portrait
    - n1452 Sanford, Terry, portrait
    - n1453 Sanford, Terry, portrait
    - n1454 Saylor, John
    - n1455 Saylor, John
    - n1456 Schafter, Thomas A.
    - n1457 Schumacher, Francis X.
    - n1458 Scott, Anne
    - n1459 Seeley, Walter J., 1938
    - n1460 Semans, Dr. James H., 1956 February
    - n1461 de Seversky, Alexander P., 1942 January 15
    - n1462 Shipman, George A., 1939
    - n1463 Missing from box
    - n1464 Shockley, Grant, Divinity
    - n1465 Shockley, Grant, Divinity
    - n1466 Sime, David
    - n1467 Smith, David T., 1959 May
    - n1468 Smith, David T., 1965 June
    - n1469 Smith, David T., 1965 June
    - n1470 Smith, David T., 1965 June
    - n1471 Smith, David T., 1965 June
    - n1472 Smith, David T., 1965 June
    - n1473 Smith, David T., 1965 June
    - n1474 copy 1 Smith, Hilrie Shelton, 1937
    - n1474 copy 2 Smith, Hilrie Shelton, 1937
    - n1475 Smith, Hilrie Shelton, 1959 September
    - n1476 Smith, Hilrie Shelton
    - n1477 Smith, Hilrie Shelton
    - n1478 Smith, Hilrie Shelton
    - n1479 Smith, Hilrie Shelton, circa 1930
    - n1480 Smith, Hilrie Shelton
    - n1481 Smith, Hilrie Shelton, 1963 March
    - n1482 Smith, Hilrie Shelton, 1963
    - n1483 Missing from box
    - n1484 Smith, Hilrie Shelton, 1963 May
    - n1485 Smith, Hilrie Shelton, 1963 May
    - n1486 Smith, J. Graham Jr., 1960 July
    - n1487 Smith, Robert S., 1965 October
    - n1488 Smith, Robert S.
    - n1489 copy 1 Smith, Mrs. Hazen, circa 1937
    - n1489 copy 2 Smith, Mrs. Hazen, circa 1937
    - n1490 Smith, Susan Gower, 1955 September
    - n1491 Smith, Willis
    - n1492 Sockman, R. W.
    - n1493 Soong, Charles J.
    - n1494 Soper, Edmund Davison, circa 1925-1928
    - n1495 Southgate, James H.
    - n1498 Spaulding, Robert L., 1965 November
    - n1499 Spears, Estelle Flowers
    - n1500 Manry, James C.
    - n1501 Manschreck, Clyde
    - n1502 Manschreck, Clyde
    - n1503 Manschreck, Clyde
    - n1504 Mancee, Joseph
    - n1505 Markham, Charles B.
    - n1506 Markham, Charles B.
    - n1507 Markham, Charles B.
    - n1508 Mattingly, Capitola
    - n1509 Maughan, William
    - n1510 Menzies, Robert, 1962
    - n1511 Menzies, Robert, 1967
    - n1512 Mims, Edwin
    - n1513 Minah, Theodore
    - n1514 Minah, Mrs. Theodore
    - n1515 Minah, Theodore
    - n1516 Mitcham, C. L.
    - n1517 Mitchell, Fannie
    - n1518 Mitchell, Fannie
    - n1519 Mitchell, Fannie
    - n1520 Mordecai, Sam F.
    - n1521 Mueller, Julia
    - n1522 Mueller, Julia
    - n1523 Murphy, C. S.
    - n1524 Murphy, C. S.
    - n1525 Murphy, Roland
    - n1526 Murray, William
    - n1527 Murray, William
    - n1528 Murray, William
    - n1529 Murray, William
    - n1530 Myers, Hiram Earl
    - n1531 Myers, Hiram Earl
    - n1532 Myers, Hiram Earl
    - n1533 Myers, Hiram Earl
    - n1534 Myers, Jack
    - n1535 Nader, Ralph
    - n1536 Nelson, Ernest William
    - n1537 Nelson, Ernest William with Hungarian String Quartet
    - n1538 Nelson, Ernest William
    - n1539 Nelson, Norman, 1963
    - n1540 Newsom, Dallas Walton, secretary to Pres. Kilgo, Washington Duke Building
    - n1541 Newsom, Dallas Walton, room 113 Epworth, 1900 January
    - n1542 Newsom, Dallas Walton, room 113 Epworth, 1900 January
    - n1543 Newsome, Clarence G., Divinity
    - n1544 Nichols, Claude, 1961
    - n1545 Nicholson, William M.
    - n1546 Nicholson, William M.
    - n1547 Nielsen, Walter M.
    - n1548 Nixon, Richard, class photo/reunion
    - n1549 Nixon, Richard, class photo/reunion
    - n1550 Nixon, Richard, class photo/reunion
    - n1551 Nixon, Richard, class photo/reunion
    - n1552 Nixon, Richard, class photo/reunion
    - n1553 Nixon, Richard, class photo/reunion
    - n1554 Nixon, Richard, residence
    - n1555 Nixon, Richard, residence, 814 6th St. (now Clarendon)
    - n1556 Nixon, Richard, student
    - n1557 Nixon, Richard, portrait
    - n1558 Nixon, Richard, portrait
    - n1559 Nixon, Richard, portrait
    - n1560 Nixon, Richard, portrait
    - n1561 Nixon, Richard, group photo
    - n1562 Nixon, Richard, group photo
    - n1563 Nixon, Richard, group photo
    - n1564 Nixon, Richard, group photo
    - n1565 Nixon, Richard, group photo
    - n1566 Nixon, Richard, group photo
    - n1567 Notling, Jan
    - n1568 Nordheim, Lothar
    - n1569 North, W. C.
    - n1570 Nuermberger, Ruth Ketring
    - n1571 Spence, Mrs. H. E. (Bessie), 1938
    - n1572 Spence, Mrs. H. E. (Bessie), 1938
    - n1573 Spence, Hersey Everett, 1962 November
    - n1574 Spence, Hersey Everett, 1938
    - n1575 Spence, Hersey Everett, Trinity class of 1907
    - n1576 Spence, Hersey Everett, circa 1937
    - n1577 Spence, Hersey Everett, 1953 November
    - n1578 Spence, Hersey Everett, 1962 November
    - n1579 Spence, Hersey Everett, circa 1952
    - n1580 Spengler, Joseph, circa 1967
    - n1581 Spengler, Joseph, 1965 December
    - n1582 Sponer, Hertha, 1958 January
    - n1583 copy 1 Sponer, Hertha, circa 1930s
    - n1583 copy 2 Sponer, Hertha, circa 1930s